# Bhavesh Shahani JAVA Backend Developer

gudd.shahani@gmail.com

+91 9575304562

• Indore,India.

in BhaveshShahani\_LinkedIn

BhaveshShahani\_Github

BhaveshShahani\_Twitter

▼ BhaveshShahani\_Portfolio



# Professional Summery

Software Developer with knowledge of web development technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Able to learn new technologies and software. Have an experience of 1000+ hours of Coding and Data Structure Algorithms. Team player who provides valuable support in a team environment.

### **Education**

Full Stack Web Developer, Masai School

Apr 2022 - 2022

**HSC,** Sanmati School 2016

**SSC,** CDS School 2014

# Certificates

• Diploma In Event Managment.

#### Technical Skills

JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS, DSA

### **Soft Skills**

Team Work, Problem Solving, Good Listener

### **d** Interests

Travelling, Hiking, Cooking

# **Experience**

**Store Manager (Partner),** *Mithi Mirchi Cafe* 2019 – 2020 | Indore, India

Worked as a Store Manager.

Sales Manager, DAYA WorldWide PVT. LTD.

2017 – 2019 | Indore, India Worked as a Sales Manager.

# Projects

# Bewakoof\_Clone

\_\_\_\_\_

Bewakoof is a lifestyle fashion brand that makes creative, distinctive fashion for the trendy, contemporary Indian, with the help of 4 members made a clone of Bewakoof.com.

# **Tech-Stack**

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.

#### Responsibility

- Product Page Design.
- Sorting.

\_\_\_\_\_

# **Body Work\_Clone**

-----

Bath & Body Work is an online eCommerce cosmetic brand, Which is a retail store chain that sells soaps, lotions, fragrances, and candles. We with the help of 4 members tried to clone the website.

# **Tech-Stack**

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT.

### Responsibility

- Team Lead
- Layout of the website
- Merging

\_\_\_\_\_